<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Containers>
  <TemplateURL>https://github.com/hy1205/unraid/blob/master/qbittorrent.xml</TemplateURL>
  <Beta>False</Beta>
  <Category>Downloaders:</Category>
  <Name>binhex-qbittorrent</Name>
  <Description>
    [b][u][span style='color: #E80000;']Description[/span][/u][/b][br]
    qBittorrent is a bittorrent client programmed in C++ / Qt that uses libtorrent (sometimes called libtorrent-rasterbar) by Arvid Norberg. It aims to be a good alternative to all other bittorrent clients out there. qBittorrent is fast, stable and provides unicode support as well as many features. This Docker image is using the headless configuration with the web frontend enabled, as well as OpenVPN to ensure a secure and private connection to the Internet, including use of iptables to prevent IP leakage when the tunnel is down. Privoxy is also included to allow unfiltered access to index sites, to use Privoxy please point your application at http://host ip:8118.[br]
    This Docker includes OpenVPN to ensure a secure and private connection to the Internet, including use of iptables to prevent IP leakage when the tunnel is down. It also includes Privoxy to allow unfiltered access to index sites, to use Privoxy please point your application at "host ip:8118"[br][br]
    [b][u][span style='color: #E80000;']Configuration[/span][/u][/b][br]
    [b]/config[/b] This is where qBittorrent will store it's configuration file, database and logs.[br]
    [b]/data[/b] This is where qBittorrent will store data downloaded, watched folder, and archived torrents.[br][br]
    [b][u][span style='color: #E80000;']Documentation[/span][/u][/b][br]
    https://github.com/binhex/documentation[br][br]
  </Description>
  <Overview>
    qBittorrent is a bittorrent client programmed in C++ / Qt that uses libtorrent (sometimes called libtorrent-rasterbar) by Arvid Norberg. It aims to be a good alternative to all other bittorrent clients out there. qBittorrent is fast, stable and provides unicode support as well as many features. This Docker image is using the headless configuration with the web frontend enabled, as well as OpenVPN to ensure a secure and private connection to the Internet, including use of iptables to prevent IP leakage when the tunnel is down. Privoxy is also included to allow unfiltered access to index sites, to use Privoxy please point your application at "http://host ip:8118".
  </Overview>
  <Registry>https://hub.docker.com/r/80x86/qbittorrent/</Registry>
  <Repository>80x86/qbittorrent:4.2.2-bullseye-amd64-nova</Repository>
  <Project>https://hub.docker.com/r/80x86/qbittorrent/</Project>
  <BindTime>true</BindTime>
  <Privileged>true</Privileged>
  <Networking>
    <Mode>host</Mode>
    <Publish>
      <Port>
        <HostPort>8082</HostPort>
        <ContainerPort>8082</ContainerPort>
        <Protocol>tcp</Protocol>
      </Port>
      <Port>
        <HostPort>8082</HostPort>
        <ContainerPort>8082</ContainerPort>
        <Protocol>udp</Protocol>
      </Port>
      <Port>
        <HostPort>8082</HostPort>
        <ContainerPort>8082</ContainerPort>
        <Protocol>tcp</Protocol>
      </Port>
      <Port>
        <HostPort>8082</HostPort>
        <ContainerPort>8118</ContainerPort>
        <Protocol>tcp</Protocol>
      </Port>
    </Publish>
    <Variable>
      <Name>STRICT_PORT_FORWARD</Name>
      <Value>yes</Value>
    </Variable>
    <Variable>
      <Name>ENABLE_PRIVOXY</Name>
      <Value>no</Value>
    </Variable>
    <Variable>
      <Name>WEBUI_PORT</Name>
      <Value>8082</Value>
    </Variable>
    <Variable>
      <Name>DEBUG</Name>
      <Value>false</Value>
    </Variable>
    <Variable>
      <Name>UMASK</Name>
      <Value>000</Value>
    </Variable>
    <Variable>
      <Name>PUID</Name>
      <Value>99</Value>
    </Variable>
    <Variable>
      <Name>PGID</Name>
      <Value>100</Value>
    </Variable>
  </Environment>
  <Data>
    <Volume>
      <HostDir>/mnt/cache/appdata/config</HostDir>
      <ContainerDir>/config</ContainerDir>
      <Mode>rw</Mode>
    </Volume>
    <Volume>
      <HostDir>/mnt/user/appdata/data</HostDir>
      <ContainerDir>/data</ContainerDir>
      <Mode>rw</Mode>
    </Volume>
  </Data>
  <WebUI>http://[IP]:[PORT:8080]/</WebUI>
  <Icon>https://github.com/hy1205/unraid/blob/master/qbittorrent.png?raw=true</Icon>
  <ExtraParams></ExtraParams>
</Containers>
